ROLI GOEL DHANUKA

Biology Teacher

PROFILE

Dedicated educator with 2.5 years' experience and a proven ability to ensure student success through differentiated instruction and creative methods of motivation. With a compassionate drive for student success, consistently crafts engaging lesson plans and supports students in exceeding expectations (even their own) and achieving goals.

CONTACT

PHONE:

91 - 7379082783

EMAIL:

roligoyal1303@gmail.com

ADDRESS: 2231 3rd Floor, Sector 23 Gurugram - 122017

HOBBIES

Reading Dancing Art & Craft

EDUCATION

D.El.Ed (UPBEB) | Noida | 2019-21 | 78%

M.Sc (Biotechnology) | Gorakhpur | 2016-18 | 75%

B.Sc (Botany, Zoology, Chemistry) | Gorakhpur | 2013-15 | 70%

WORK EXPERIENCE

Teacher

SANSKRITI SCHOOL, Gurugram (Jun 2022 onwards)

PGT Biology Teacher

NAVALS NATIONAL ACADEMY SENIOR SECONDARY SCHOOL, Gorakhpur (Apr 2017-18)

TGT Science Teacher

NAVALS NATIONAL ACADEMY SENIOR SECONDARY SCHOOL, Gorakhpur (Mar 2015-17)

EXPERIMENTAL LEARNING & AWARDS

- Presented project in International Institute of Biotechnology
- Presented project in national conference on "plant Science research in 21st century: Challenges and strategies"
- Teacher of the Year 2017

SKILLS

